we will begin this exercise with a three -to -one method find
a comfortable position close your eyes take a deep breath and
while exhaling mentally repeat and visualize the number three
three times.
To help you learn to relax physically at level three, I'm going
to direct your attention to different parts of your body.
Relax your scalp.
relax your forehead relax your eyes and the tissue surrounding
your eyes with a slight smile relax your face relax your throat
and neck area externally and internally relax your shoulders
arms and hands
Take a deep breath, and as you exhale, relax your chest
externally and internally.
take a deep breath and as you exhale relax your abdominal area
externally and internally
Relax your thighs Relax your knees
relax your calves
relax your feet
you are now at a deeper healthier level of mind deeper than
before this is your physical relaxation level three whenever you
mentally repeat and visualize the number three your body will
relax as completely as you are now and more so every time
you practice
to enter mental relaxation level 2 take a deep breath and while
exhaling mentally repeat and visualize number 2 3 times and you
are at level 2 a deeper level in three level two is
for mental relaxation where noises will not distract you instead
noises will help you to relax mentally more and more to improve
mental relaxation at level two practice visualizing tranquil and
passive scenes in a holographic three -dimensional manner
engaging all of your subjective senses do that now
take another deep breath and while exhaling mentally repeat and
visualize number one three times you are now at level one the
basic plane level a deeper healthier level of mind
to help you enter a deeper healthier level of mind I'm going
to count from ten to one on each descending number you will
feel yourself going deeper and you will enter a deeper
healthier level of mind ten nine feel going deeper eight seven
six deeper and deeper.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Deeper and deeper.
Two.
One.
You are now at a deeper, healthier level of mind deeper than
before it is a wonderful feeling to be deeply relaxed a very
healthy state of being
effective sensory projection statements for success
i will be speaking in your place
I am now able to function my intelligence by developing my
sensing faculties and to experience myself as any point place
level or depth so as to be aware of any actions taking
place I am able to function in non locality regarding time and
space I am aware that intelligence exists at all levels and
depths in the universe and therefore I can attune to all
information I
I am now able to use my sensing faculties and to experience
myself as any matter kingdom,
mineral, plant, animal and human if this is what I desire to
do.
I am now able to detect abnormalities whenever such
abnormalities exist within any kingdom, any level any depth I am
now able to apply corrective measures and to bring back to
normalcy any abnormality found within any Kingdom any level and
any depth quantum energy is available at any level to be acted
upon to create through through the subjective and objective
dimensions.
We will now impress new information for your benefit, the mental
screen.
To locate your mental screen, begin with your eyes closed, turn
slightly upward from the horizontal plane of sight at an angle
of approximately 20 degrees.
The area that you perceive with your mind is your mental screen.
Without using your eyelids as screens, sense your mental screen
to be out away from your body.
To improve To improve the use of your mental screen, project
images or mental pictures onto the screen, especially images
having color.
Concentrate on mentally sensing and visualizing true color.
Programming the HoloViewing technique that you can use for
problem solving.
Whenever you need to solve a problem, make a decision, or obtain
guidance with the Holoviewing technique, proceed in the
following manner.
Project the image of the problem or present situation onto your
mental screen as a two -dimensional dull gray tone image similar
to a black and white Polaroid photograph in order to make a
brief study of the problem.
Make the problem image smaller, smaller and smaller
until it completely disappears.
At that moment when the problem image disappears
create an image of the solution and allow it to approach you
by making it bigger and bigger be sure to project a bright
clear and colorful dynamic solution image stop the approaching
image and modify improve or change any element of the image that
needs improvement.
When the image of the solution is exactly as you desire it
to be continue allowing it to approach you by getting bigger
still until it wraps around you and you find yourself within the
image in a holographic three three -dimensional experience with
a 360 -degree spherical view.
At this point, you may experience yourself fully and completely,
engaging all of your mental senses together with coherent
emotions.
You may also experience yourself in a second -person point of
view. In other words, you may experience the solution image from
the other person or person's point of view. In addition, you may
also project yourself outside the scene and experience observing
the solution image from a third -person perspective, the
observer.
This allows you to have a full holographic experience that you
can then move forward into the future through hollow movement
experiencing the solution in a past tense sense from the
perspective of whole and complete.
mentally talk to source energy within you and through the hollow
viewing technique share your desires charged with coherent
emotions with your source energy express great gratitude
gratitude, appreciation,
compassion or love to source energy deep within you.
Take for granted that your source energy will assist you with
manifesting your solution.
During the next three days, look for indications that point to
the solution.
every time you think of the project think of the solution that
you have created with the hollow viewing technique and do so in
a past tense sense it is time to work on one problem
case using the hollow viewing technique project the image of the
problem or present situation onto your mental screen as a two
-dimensional dull gray tone image
similar to a black and white Polaroid photograph in order to
make a brief study of the problem.
make the problem image smaller smaller and smaller until it
completely disappears at that moment when the problem image
disappears create an image of the solution and allow it to
approach you by making it bigger and bigger be sure to project
a bright clear colorful and dynamic solution image
stop the approaching image and modify improve or change any
element of the image that needs improvement created exactly how
you wish it to be
when the image of the solution is exactly as you desire it
to be continue allowing it to approach you by getting bigger and
bigger still until it wraps around you and you find yourself
within the image in a holographic three -dimensional experience
with a 360 -degree spherical view.
Take a deep breath and relax.
At this point, experience yourself fully and completely,
engaging all of your mental senses together with coherent
emotions.
Bring about desire, belief and expectation, faith.
You may also experience yourself in a second person point of
view.
In other words, you may experience the solution image from the
other person or person's point of view.
In addition, you may also project yourself outside the scene and
experience observing the solution image from a third -person
perspective the observer engage in the experience fully and
completely in a holographic manner that you can then move
forward into the future through hollow movement experiencing the
solution in a past tense sense from the perspective of whole and
complete
mentally talk to source energy within you and through the hall
of you in technique share your desires charged with coherent
emotions emotions.
expressions, expressions,
expressions. compassion and a love to source energy deep within
you for being there with you and for you every step of
the way
Take for granted that your source energy will assist you with
manifesting your solution.
During the next three days, look for indications that point to
the solution. every time you think of the project think of the
solution that you created with a hollow viewing technique do so
in a past tense sense and expect this or better than this
to manifest
Every time you function at these levels of the mind, you will
receive beneficial effects physically and mentally.
You may use these levels of the mind to help yourself, to
help your loved ones and to help any human being who needs
help physically and mentally.
You will always use these levels of the mind in a constructive,
creative manner for all that is good, honest, pure, clean, and
positive, and this is so.
you will continue to strive to take part in constructive and
creative activities to make this a better world to live in so
that when you move on you shall have left behind a better
world for those who follow you will consider the whole of
humanity depending Depending on their ages, as fathers or
mothers, brothers or sisters, sons or daughters, you are a
superior human being. You have greater understanding,
compassion, and patience with others.
in a moment I'm going to count from one to five and
cause a sound with my fingers at that moment you will open
your eyes be wide awake feeling fine and in perfect health
feeling better than than before one two coming out slowly now
three at the count of five you will open your eyes be
wide awake feeling fine and in perfect health feeling better
than before feeling the way you feel when you have slept the
right amount of revitalizing, refreshing, relaxing, healthy
sleep.
Four, five, eyes open, wide awake, feeling fine and in perfect
health, feeling better than before.
To guarantee success with your Silva techniques, we recommend
that you take the Silva seminars live. For more information over
course schedules and locations, log on to silvamethod .com or
call 1 -800 -545 -6463 within the continental United States or
956 -722 -6391.
Thank you.